Nighttime and Idols
Ramen
Yes ...
Ramen is really a must in my life.
It's already an indispensable part of my life.
Do I go out to eat it or make it?
I love to make it at home.
I can go out to eat ramen
I don't go out much.
I eat ramen and come home
play games and go to bed.
That's great!
I'll probably drink and play games.
I thought of everything.
Ramen noodles.
What kind of ramen do you like?
I like pretty much all of them.
The one I like the most right now is tripeitan.
I like it very thick.
That's good.
Horror lemon!
And in the Kansai area...
I have some nighttime knowledge.
There's something called "awa-kei" in the Kansai area.
I have an image that it hasn't come to Kansai yet
I have an image of it.
What do you think of it?
I like it very much.
There are a lot of awa-kei restaurants in the tri-paitan area.
New restaurants are opening all the time.
Abalone restaurants...
There's always a long line of people waiting in line.
Heh...
It's hard to find awa-kei restaurants in the Kanto area.
What a waste!What a waste!
Someone take it to Tokyo!
That's right.
I've always wanted to try it, but I've never had it before.
It's delicious. You should come.
Takada's a fool, huh? It's very popular.
Takada no Baba.
I've never been there.
What's there to eat at Takada no Baba?
Takada no Baba has a lot of ramen noodles.
It's a famous place.
I see.
You should go there.
They have Jiro-style ramen.
I like Jiro, too.
You can go here, too?
I love it.
Osaka is a ramen town.
Yes, yes.
I love it.
Put some meat in the teruko.
Yes, definitely.
Vegetables too!
Yes, yes.
And the usual amount of vegetables.
And definitely a raw egg.
Stick it in the middle and eat it.
I know, I know.
I love that too.
You go alone?
I go alone.
I can even go to a Jiro-style restaurant by myself.
You have a lot of ramen friends.
Ramen.
I have friends I go out for ramen with.
I have a ramen network.The Ramen Network.
Yes, sir.
When you come to Kanto for work or something.
Or when you go to Hokkaido, as I mentioned earlier, for a location shoot...
Do you go there and check out the ramen?
Yes, I will.
Whenever I have free time, I'll definitely check it out.
I did that today.
I was thinking of going in early.
Which places came up on your list?
Something on the main road over there.
Thai ramen?
Like the snapper ramen.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see...
Are you a ramen lover, Mr. Yakan?
I'm actually in the ramen family.
That's right, we're friends!
We're friends!
We're in this together!
I'm with you!
Tell me about it!
Please tell me!
If it's ramen in Tokyo, I know what it is!
I'm so happy!
So I know the ramen at Umechan Kimba.
Please tell me!
I've already said I'm OK with ramen!
I'm already OK with ramen!
You've already said yes to ramen!
Everything is fine.
No accidents.
No accidents, so far.
This program is...
Mr. Okoyan
Mr. Channao.Channao-san
Mr. hy007
Mr. Sagarei
Sent to you courtesy of Mr. Caspenter.
Thank you for watching!
Bye bye!